AI DevCon is the conference [music]
for thought leaders shaping the way that
software development is accelerating
into the agentic future. In June, we
hosted a sold-out event in London, and
this November, we're coming back for our
second [music]
New York conference. We'd love for you
to join us. We're looking for
experience-driven [music]
talks that show how agentic coding works
in the real world at real [music]
companies.
Go to tessell.io/devcon
to complete the CFP.
Early submissions will have the highest
chance of being accepted, [music] but we
all know how fast this landscape's
moving, so we're keeping submissions
open until October 1st.
I can't wait to read through all the
amazing topics that I know [music]
you're going to submit, and I can't wait
to see them at DevCon this November.